ARAWN DAVIES

Address · Phone

arawn@arawn-davies.co.uk · www.linkedin.com/in/arawn-davies· www.arawn-davies.co.uk

An efficient communicator and able to work in a team as both a leader and a team member, with extensive experience in many IT roles. Coming from a multilingual and multinational family of Welsh and Indian descent, I have experience at helping people who speak English as a second language in aiding them with their problems and needs. I am an ambitious, highly motivated, and intelligent young man who takes pride in delivering work to the best of my ability. With a kind, friendly and approachable personality, I take pride in providing excellent support to people. Highly proficient worker with 10 years using a vast range of different programming languages, software suites and hardware equipment, I can easily adapt and become familiar with any new platform used in my work.

SKILLS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

- Communication and thinking outside the box
- Full UK Driving License
- Linux, Git, virtualization, LAMP, UNIX and embedded electronics
- DBS checked

- Experienced in IT, electronics, and IT tutoring
- Fluent in English
- Experienced in languages C/C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, HTML, PHP, Assembly, and .NET.

EXPERIENCE

AUG 2021 - SEPT 2021

CUSTOMER SUPPORT SPECIALIST, COMMUNITY BRANDS UK

Providing customer support for several MIS platforms to hundreds of schools across the UK, triaging issues with engineers and helping prioritize urgent cases.

JUNE 2015 - OCT 2021

DIRECTOR, ADX TECHNOLOGIES

Provider of specialist technical support for many different platforms and other personal computing devices and networks

MAY 2019 - AUG 2019

ELECTRICIAN + ENGINEERING WORKER, FREELANCE

Worked in the local community in Harlech, North Wales. I helped outdoor structures and installed light fixtures, wall sockets, telecommunications and other IT technical support for different customers.

EDUCATION

SEP 2014 - JUL 2016

GCSES, WIGSTON COLLEGE

Certificate in Digital Applications (CiDA) B Electronics, Maths & Music B Double Science B/C

SEP 2016 - JUN 2017

GCSES, REGENT COLLEGE

ICT Distinction Star English A*/B Business Studies B

Psychology C

FURTHER EDUCATION

SEP 2017 – JUN 2019

A LEVELS. WYGGESTON QUEEN ELIZABETH I COLLEGE

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma, Distinction-Distinction-Merit Equivalent of 3 A-levels at AAB

OCT 2020 - PRESENT

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE DEGREE, DE MONTFORT UNIVERSITY

Computer Science BSc. 3 years with a placement

ACTIVITIES

JAN 2020 – MAR 2020

VOLUNTEER. LOROS SPIRAL SCRATCH

I volunteered at the local LOROS Hospice music charity store in Leicester, I authorized sales, aided in organization of donations, stock, listing and serving customers with any questions they may have.

SEP 2016 - PRESENT

AUDIO ENGINEER. FREELANCE

As a multi-instrumentalist, I combine my extensive IT software and hardware skills in addition to my music knowledge to provide digital audio workstation, computer & music audio equipment services to several local customers.

PROJECTS

CREATOR, MEDLI OPERATING SYSTEM

For almost a decade, I have been developing an operating system in my spare time for PCs in C# and .NET. This has been a major project of mine as it has aided in my learning and practical use of skills which I have learned over my career and education history. This can be seen at www.github.com/Siarantie-Solutions/Medli

CORE TEAM MEMBER, COSMOS (C# OPEN-SOURCE MANAGED OPERATING SYSTEM)

In addition to working on my operating system Medli, I have been working alongside a group of other highly experienced developers to develop a toolkit for other developers to create full fledged operating systems using existing applications and source code. This can be seen at www.github.com/CosmosOS/Cosmos

FOUNDER, SIARANITE SOLUTIONS

As an umbrella organization that manages Medli, I also use this organization to manage my other software projects that I have developed and created over the years. These include assembler byte-code virtual machines for embedded devices, compiler deployment scripts, and file systems for storing and managing data on storage devices. You can see a list of these projects www.github.com/Siaranite-Solutions